https://www.hitechcaddservices.com/privacy-policy/

Request Quote »Who we areOverviewManagementHistory & MilestonesClients & TestimonialsServicesArchitectural CAD Services2D Drafting Services3D VisualizationInterior DesignStructural ServicesShop Drawings for Steel FabricationSteel Detailing ServicesConstruction DocumentationMEP ServicesMEP BIM ServicesMEP Clash DetectionBIM ServicesBIM Consulting Services3D BIM ModelingConstruction Scheduling (4D)Cost Estimation (5D)Point Cloud to BIMRevit Family CreationCPQ SolutionsVisual ConfigurationDesign AutomationDriveWorks ImplementationDriveWorks ExtensionsTacton ImplementationMillwork DetailingCabinet DraftingKitchen Millwork & JoineryWoodwork CAD DraftingEngineering DesignMechanical Design & DraftingCAD Conversion Services3D CAD ModelingSheet Metal DesignPressure Vessel DesignRapid PrototypingReverse EngineeringCFD Analysis ServicesFEA Analysis ServicesIndustriesAutomotive EngineeringBuilding ConstructionHotels & ResortsHealthcare BuildingResidential BuildingCommercial BuildingRetail BuildingInstitutional BuildingInfrastructureAirport DesignBridge DesignRail EngineeringRoads and Highway DesignPlant EngineeringHeavy MachineryCase StudiesBuilding Information Modeling (BIM)Architectural Drafting & 3D VisualizationStructural Drafting & Steel DetailingMEP Drafting & ModelingMechanical Design & DraftingDesign AutomationBlogContact UsRequest Quote »
HomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyEffective date: 23rd May 2018IntroductionHitech iSolutions LLP and its subsidiaries (collectively “we”, “us” and “our”) take the privacy and security of your personal information very seriously. This Privacy Notice applies to our collection and use of personal information through our website and through our offline business-related interactions with you. Note that this Privacy Notice does not apply to that we process for employment purposes other than resumes and related information that you provide us through our websites.We may change this Privacy Notice from time to time. Therefore, we may ask you to check this Privacy Notice occasionally to ensure that you are aware of the most recent version. We will notify you of any changes where we are required to do so.
Hitech iSolutions LLP is GDPR compliantInformation We May Collect About You:Personal InformationWe may collect and process personal information you provide us, such as First and last name, Title / Position / Designation, Company Name, Contact information (company email, work address, work phone) & Call recording datawhen you:Complete an online form (e.g., to obtain email updates or ask us to send you information, submit business request, or participate in a survey);Provide information to us offline regarding our business-related interactions with youWe may also receive personal information about you from other sources, which could include commercially available sources, such as public databases and data aggregators to the extent permitted by applicable data protection laws.By providing us with your sensitive personal information, you consent to us processing that information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Notice or any collection notice provided to you.
User ConsentThe privacy policy is applicable to all the visitors of this website, and users are requested to fully read and understand the terms and conditions within the policy. By using this website, it is considered that visitors confirm their consent to the collection, use and dissemination of information in line with this privacy policy. If the terms and conditions of this privacy policy, in general or in particular, are not acceptable to any user then we suggest immediate suspension of the use of this website by such users.Technical InformationWe may collect information about your browser and/or device that you use to access our Sites (like the type of browser and browser settings and the device identification number). Device information may or may not be personally identifiable depending upon whether it is linked to the identity of the user.We may also automatically log information, such as your IP address, domain name, browser type, date and time of access, and other log file data. This information may be used to analyse trends and help us with administration of our Sites. We may collect statistical or non-personally-identifiable information about you including, for example, which pages you visit, how long you remain on a particular page, the website from which you came to our Site, or similar information.We also may collect aggregate information such as the total number of unique or return visitors to our Sites, or visiting a section of the Site within a given timeframe. We may also use this information to measure the use of our Sites to improve our content.Our site use Google Analytics cookies. Information collected by these cookies will be transferred to and stored by Google on servers in the USA in accordance with its privacy practices.If you do not want us to deploy browser cookies to your device when you visit our Sites, you may set the browser to reject cookies or to notify the user when a web site tries to place cookies in the browser program. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use some features offered on our Sites.How We Use the Personal Information You Provide to UsSubject to applicable data protection laws, we may use your personal information for the following purposes:To provide you with the services and information offered through our Sites;To process your requests and respond to your inquiries;Register you for any services you have signed up for;For business administration, including statistical analysis and as may be required to perform our obligations under a contractual relationship with you.To improve our Sites by helping us understand who uses the Site;To contact you about products and services offered by us which we believe may interest you andFor fraud prevention and detection and to comply with applicable laws, regulations or codes of practice.Who Will Have Access to Your Personal Information?Your personal information may be made available within the Hitech iSolutions LLP. They may need access to your personal information to perform their functions but will not use your personal information for any other purpose.We may also disclose Personal Data to comply with our legal or regulatory obligations, in response to a non-mandatory request for information made by a governmental or state body, or as part of an investigation of unlawful activity.Disclosure of information to third partiesAt no time do we provide your personal information to any person or entity outside of Hitech iSolutions LLP. The only exception to this would involve a circumstance where we would be compelled to by law enforcement, regulatory or other government agencies in order to comply with legal or regulatory obligations or requests. By providing information through the Hitech website you are consenting to the disclosures described above.Security and Retention of Your Personal InformationThe security of your personal information is important to us. We take reasonable steps, including technical, administrative and physical safeguards, designed to protect the personal information submitted to us from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.We may retain your personal information for as long as your contact with you is active or as needed for the specific business purpose for which it was collected. In some cases, we may be required to retain information to comply with laws or regulations or other legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.International Data TransfersYour personal information may be transferred to countries located outside your country or region, including to countries that may not provide a similar or adequate level of protection to that provided by your country or region. By using the Site or otherwise providing personal information to us, you hereby expressly consent to the transfer of your personal information outside your country or region.
MarketingWe may contact you periodically by email to provide information regarding services and content that may be of interest to you. If applicable law requires that we receive your explicit consent before we send you certain types of marketing communications, we will only send you those types of communications after receiving your explicit consent. If you wish to stop receiving these types of communications from us, you can opt-out by contacting us at the email and address as described below or use any mechanism provided in the communication that you receive.Access, Correction and Other Individual RightsWith your support, we will keep your personal information accurate and up-to-date. If we process your personal information, then you may have a right under data privacy laws to remove, amend, or correct your personal information at any time, subject to certain exceptions permitted by law. You also may have other rights including rights to object to or to restrict the processing of your personal data and data portability. You may also contact us to opt-out from any program or other service for which you may have registered via our sites. If you would like to access, correct or delete the personal information we hold about you, please contact us as described below.Contact UsWe are GDPR & HIPAA compliant and enforce our privacy policy strictly. Contact us at privacy@hitechos.com if you have any questions about our privacy policy.
Get a Free Quote
By checking this box; I understand and agree to be communicated for the said and mentioned purpose of business and/ or service provision by the domain owner.
12+12=?
India: +91-794-000-3252
USA: +1-408-338-8047 Hi-Tech House, Near Gurukul Tower
Gurukul, Ahmedabad- 380 052 (India) Contact Us
Sitemap | Privacy Policy |
Contact Us
Copyright © 2020
Hitech CADD Services. All Rights Reserved.
Email: info@hitechcaddservices.com
Follow us:
Who we areOverviewManagementHistory & MilestonesClients & TestimonialsServicesArchitectural CAD Services2D Drafting Services3D VisualizationInterior DesignStructural ServicesShop Drawings for Steel FabricationSteel Detailing ServicesConstruction DocumentationMEP ServicesMEP BIM ServicesMEP Clash DetectionBIM ServicesBIM Consulting Services3D BIM ModelingConstruction Scheduling (4D)Cost Estimation (5D)Point Cloud to BIMRevit Family CreationCPQ SolutionsVisual ConfigurationDesign AutomationDriveWorks ImplementationDriveWorks ExtensionsTacton ImplementationMillwork DetailingCabinet DraftingKitchen Millwork & JoineryWoodwork CAD DraftingEngineering DesignMechanical Design & DraftingCAD Conversion Services3D CAD ModelingSheet Metal DesignPressure Vessel DesignRapid PrototypingReverse EngineeringCFD Analysis ServicesFEA Analysis ServicesIndustriesAutomotive EngineeringBuilding ConstructionHotels & ResortsHealthcare BuildingResidential BuildingCommercial BuildingRetail BuildingInstitutional BuildingInfrastructureAirport DesignBridge DesignRail EngineeringRoads and Highway DesignPlant EngineeringHeavy MachineryCase StudiesBuilding Information Modeling (BIM)Architectural Drafting & 3D VisualizationStructural Drafting & Steel DetailingMEP Drafting & ModelingMechanical Design & DraftingDesign AutomationBlogContact Us
Discuss your Challenges
Email us!Connect with us
Facebook
linkedin
twitter
instagram
youtube
